Smith
The College of Saint Rose Archives
Smith, Ursula Rita Casey, Papers
1920-1998
Smith
The College of Saint Rose Archives
1.25 Linear feet (3 boxes: 2 smaller boxes in 1 larger box)
This collection consists of materials that we found in Ursula Smith's home upon her passing in early 1999. The collection offers a unique glimpse into the evolution of The College of Saint Rose since its founding in 1920. The collection also illustrates the different aspects of the college that Ursula Smith found important and worth remembering. The collection traces her evolution from Saint Rose Student, to Saint Rose parent, to Saint Rose patroness.
Biographical/Historical note
Ursula Rita Casey Smith (1902-1999) was a member of the first graduating class of The College of Saint Rose. Her sister and a member of the Sisters of St. Joseph of Carondelet, Sister Rita Agnes Casey (1893-1960), was one of the founders of the college. Her daughter, Sister Rose Regina Smith (formerly Maryrose Smith) was the first child of a Saint Rose alumna, graduated in 1950, and has worked at the College of Saint Rose for over twenty years. She also had two other daughters who graduated from the College of Saint Rose: Ann Smith Malloy (class of 1951) and Ursula Smith McKegney (class of 1957). Her husband, Edward "Duke" Smith was among the first men to attend the College of Saint Rose, as part of an evening education program aimed at veterans.
Scope and Contents note
The Ursula Rita Casey Smith Collection contains the memorabilia and mementos that Ursula felt compelled to hold onto throughout her life. The collection spans several decades and reflects the important role that The College of Saint Rose played in her life.
The collection contains College of Saint Rose memorabilia, photographs, a handmade photo album for Chi Mu Kappa, a sorority created for the members of the first graduating class of the college. The collection also contains newspaper clippings related to the college and its alumni, as well as clippings related to herself, her daughter, Sister Rose Regina Smith, as well as her sister, Sister Rita Agnes Casey. The collection also contains programs from Rose Day events, musical programs and theater productions, and commencement programs from the college. Also within the collection are personal correspondence in the form of greeting cards, as well as letters related to the College of Saint Rose alumni association, and issues surrounding the upheaval at The College of Saint Rose in the late 1960s -early 1970s. Also included in the collection are memorial cards and cards sent to her parents by Sister Rita Agnes Casey.
While the collection is broad in scope and spans many decades, it does not reflect the College of Saint Rose as a whole, but rather aspects of the College of Saint Rose and how the college, in turn, affected the life of one individual. This collection is unique because it belonged to one of the founding students of the College of Saint Rose, a woman who valued her own education as well as the college itself. The collection is also a reflection on the evolution of Catholic college education and the education of women in the 20th century.
Arrangement note
The collection is organized into the following series:
Newspaper Clippings, 1950-1995
Photographs, 1921-1950s
Saint Rose Publications, 1954-1973
Rose Day Publications, 1943-1957
Textbooks, 1920-1923
Class Notes, 1924
Book Covers, undated
Report Cards, 1920-1923
Tuition Receipts, 1948-1957
Personal Correspondence, 1921-1996
Religious Memorial Cards and Prayer Cards, 1939-1990
Hand-lettered Miniatures, undated
Saint Rose Event Programs, Flyers and Posters, 1922-1995
Commencement Programs and Publications, 1957
The College of Saint Rose College Catalogs, 1920
General Correspondence, 1947-1995
Alumni Association, 1934-1990
Archconfraternity of St. Joseph Norbertine Order, 1979
Diplomas and Awards, 1946 and 1985-1986
Memorabilia, 1926-1995
Conditions Governing Access note
There are no access restrictions to this collection.
Separated Materials note
An extensive volume of materials was removed and added to other collections. A list of the items, the series they were taken from, and the collection they were moved to is as follows.
From Series 2: Photographs
Photograph of President Thomas Manion sitting at his desk. The photograph is attached to a paper with the heading, "What do you mean I have to ask the faculty."
Moved to: Photograph Collection
Pen and ink drawings of St. Joseph's Hall with associated text: "This print of St. Joseph's Hall is the first in a series of four scenes of the College to be given yearly by the Alumni Association to members of the President's Club."
Moved to: Oversize Collection
From Series 3: College of Saint Rose Publications
Canary Trills
Moved to Student Publications: Canary Trills
"Canary Trills," December 8, 1921
CSR Update
Moved to Alumni Publications: CSR Updates
"CSR Update: The Hellman Gift.. .A Neighbor Remembers." Vol. IV, No. 3. 1981?
Delta Epsilon Sigma - Alpha Chi Chapter
Moved to Delta Epsilon Sigma Records
"Delta Epsilon Sigma Alpha Chi Chapter," Program, April 21,1951 (2 copies)
"Spring Meeting, Alpha Chi Chapter, Delta Epsilon Sigma," Program, May 3, 1958
"Delta Epsilon Sigma - Alpha Chi Chapter presents Delta Day," Program, April 7, 1973
Development Office Publications
Moved to Office of Development, 1964 -
"A Tradition of Giving." CSR, The College of Saint Rose, copyright MCMLXXXIX
CSR Annual Fund Prospectus: 1986-1987
Family Rosary Bulletin
Moved to the Family Rosary Crusade folder
"Family Rosary Bulletin," May 25, 1951
Family Rosary Crusade, Family Prayer Rosary Rally, February 15, 1953
Gadfly
Moved to the Student Newspapers: Gadfly
"Gadfly." Vol. XXXVIII, March 26, 1974.
Genesis
Moved to the Office of Public Information Publications: Genesis
"Genesis." Vol. 2, Issue 3. Summer, 1985
"Genesis." Vol. 14, No. 1. Spring, 1997
Inscape
Moved to the Student Newspapers: Inscape
"Inscape." Vol. XXXIII, No. 10, March 6, 1970
“Inscape." Vol. XXXIV, No. 1. September 21,1970
"Inscape." Vol. XXXV, No. 7, February 25, 1972.
"Inscape." Vol. XXXV No. 8, March 10, 1972. (2 copies)
Keynote
Moved to the Alumni Publications: Keynote
"Keynote." Vol. 2, No. 2. Winter, 1968
”Keynote." Vol. 4, No. 3. Spring, 1970
"Keynote." Vol. 4, No. 4. Summer, 1970
"Keynote." Vol. 5, No. 5. Fall, 1970
The Newsletter
Moved to Alumni Publications: Newsletter
"The Newsletter." Vol. 2, No. 1. September, 1971
"The Newsletter." Vol. 3, No. 2. May, 1972
Rambler
Moved to the Student Publications: Rambler
"Rambler." Silver Jubilee, 1945. Vol. 17, No. 3-4
"Rambler." Vol. XXIII, No. 1. Christmas, 1950
"Rambler." Vol. XXIII, No. 2. Easter, 1951
"Rambler." Vol. XXIII, No. 3. Graduation, 1951
"Rambler." Vol. XXVI, No. 2. Easter, 1954
"Rambler." Vol. XXVIII, No. 1. Winter, 1955
"Rambler." Vol. XXX, No. 2. Spring, 1957
"Rambler." Vol. XXXIV, No. 1. Christmas, 1961
Rosaverian - Regular Newspapers
Moved to Student Newspapers: Rosaverian
"Rosaverian." Jubilee Edition. Vol. IX, No. 2. 1945
"Rosaverian." Vol. XVI, No. 4. November 12, 1952 (2 copies)
"Rosaverian." Vol. XVII, No. 4. November 11,1953
"Rosaverian." Vol. XVII, No. 6. December 15, 1953
"Rosaverian Shopping Guide," September 19, 1955
"Rosaverian." Vol. XX. No. 13. June 1957
"Rosaverian." Vol. XXI, No. 2, October 2, 1957
"Rosaverian." Vol. XX, No. 4, October 30, 1957
"Rosaverian." Vol. XXI, No. 5. November 19, 1957
"Rosaverian." Vol. XXII, No. 2, October 13, 1958
"Rosaverian." Vol. XXII, No. 3, November 11, 1958
"Rosaverian." Vol. XXII, No. 5, February 10, 1959
Rosaverian - Commencement Issues
Moved to: Rose Day Box, Rosaverian Folder
"Rosaverian." Commencement - 1942. Vol. Ill, No. 13. June 1, 1942
"Rosaverian." Commencement, 1951
"Rosaverian." Vol. XVIII, No. 14. June, 1955 Commencement
"Rosaverian," Vol. XX, No. 13, June, 1957 Commencement
Rosetta
Moved to the Alumni Publications: Rosetta
"Rosetta." Vol. XII, No. 1, May 1946
"Rosetta." Vol. XIII, May 1947
"Rosetta." Vol. XIV. October 1948
"Rosetta." Vol. XVI, No. 4. October 15, 1951
"Rosetta." Vol. XVIII, No. 3. October 5, 1953
"Rosetta." Vol. XXI, No. 4. December, 1956
"Rosetta." Vol. XXIII, No. 5. March, 1958
"Rosetta." Vol. XXIII, No. 2. May, 1958
"Rosetta." Vol. XXV, No. 3. October, 1959
"Rosetta." Vol. XXVI, No. 2 May, 1960
"Rosetta." Vol. XXV, No. 3. October, 1960
"Rosetta." Vol. XXV, No. 4. December, 1960
"Rosetta." Vol. XXVI, No. 1. February, 1961 (2 copies)
"Rosetta." Vol. XXVI, No. 1. February, 1962
"Rosetta." Vol. XXIX, No. 2. May, 1964
The College of Saint Rose Student Handbooks
Moved to the Student Handbook Collection
Student Handbook, 1948-1949, College of Saint Rose
Student Senate Handbook, 1953-1954, College of Saint Rose
Student Handbook, 1954-1955, College of Saint Rose
Student Handbook, 1955-1956, College of Saint Rose
Student Handbook, 1956-1957, College of Saint Rose
Student Handbook, 1970-1971, College of Saint Rose
Student Handbook, 1975-1976, Bicentennial Year at CSR
Siena College Student Hand Books
Donated to Siena College
Student Hand Book, 1957-1958, Siena College
Student Hand Book, 1958-1959, Siena College
Student Hand Book, 1959-1960, Siena College
Sodality of Our Lady Publications
Moved to the Sodality of Our Lady Records
"Famous Living Paintings of Madonnas," May 18, 1947 (2 copies)
"Marian Petals," Vol. 5, No. 8, May 22, 1951
"Sixth Annual Regional Marian Congress," organized by the Mariology Commission, March 15, 1953
"Career Week, March 15-17, 1954," presented by The Sodality of Our Lady
"Mariology Commission, New York - New Jersey Region, National Federation of Catholic College Students, College of Saint Rose, November, 1954." [This is a publication offering advice to encourage students to use the rosary and carry the rosary.]
"Mariology Commission, New York - New Jersey Region, National Federation of Catholic College Students, College of Saint Rose, April, 1955."
"Mariology Commission, New York - New Jersey Region, National Federation of Catholic College Students, College of Saint Rose, November, 1955."
"Blueprint: College of Saint Rose Sodality News," Vol. I, No. 2, December, 1956
"Blueprint: College of Saint Rose Sodality News," Vol. II, No. 1, November, 1957 " "Blueprint: College of Saint Rose Sodality News," Vol. II, No. 2, December 1957
Correspondence regarding the story of "Our Lady of the Rosary," Undated
From Series 4; College of Saint Rose's Rose Day Publications
Moved to: Rose Day Box - Programs
Rose Day, June 12, 1926 Program
Rose Day, June 9, 1928 Program
Rose Day, June 6, 1936 Program
Rose Day, June 5, 1937 Program
Rose Day, June 3, 1939 Program (2 copies)
Rose Day, June 1, 1940 Program (2 copies)
Rose Day, June 7, 1941 Program
Rose Day, May 30, 1942 Program
Rose Day, May 29, 1943 Program
Rose Day, Commemorating Silver Jubilee, June 2, 1945
Rose Day, June 7, 1947 Program
Rose Day, June 5, 1948 Program
Rose Day, June 4, 1949 Program
Rose Day, June 2, 1951 Program
Rose Queen, May 31, 1952 Program (2 copies)
Rose Queen, May 30, 1953 Program
Rose Queen, 1954 Program (2 copies)
"Rosaverian." Vol. XIX, No. 14. June, 1956 (2 copies)
Rose Queen, 1957 Program
Rose Queen, 1958 Program (3 copies)
Rose Queen, 1959 Program
Rose Day, 1960 Program
Rose Day, 1961 Program
From Series 8: College of Saint Rose Event Programs, Flyers and Posters
Art
Moved to the Art Collection
Invitation to photography exhibit, "Love calls us to the things of this world," Novembers, 1972
Art listing and price guide for photography exhibit, "Love calls us to the things of this world," November 5-25, [1972]
Building Dedications - Campus Center
Moved to House Histories: 420-430 Western, Campus Center
Invitation, Dedication and Inspection of the New Campus Center, September 10, 1964
Building Dedications - New Residence Halls
Moved to House Histories: 939, 941, 943 Madison Ave. Townhouses (Riley, Carondelet,
Cavanaugh)
Dedication of the New Residence Halls, Saturday, April 9, 1983
Campaign for Saint Rose
Moved to Office of Development, 1964 -: Campaign for Saint Rose
Invitation, Gala of the Campaign for Saint Rose, May 31, 1990
Convocations
Moved to Academics and Honors Convocations and Related Materials Collection
Anniversary Convocation Program, April 9, 1954
Honors Convocation Program, May 9, 1974
Honors Convocation, Notes on Faculty/Student Awards and Achievements for 1974-75
Academic Convocation Program, January 27, 1995
Debates
Moved to Debate Team folder
"Intercollegiate Debate: Hamilton College vs. College of Saint Rose." March 13, 1936. Document is torn.
Drama
Moved to Drama Collection
Shadows, "Shakespeare's 'Much Ado About Nothing,'" May 16-17,1932
Shadows, "Shakespeare's 'Love's Labor Lost,'" January 17-18, 1933
Shadows, "Shakespeare's Twelfth Night," April 17-18, [1933]
Shadows, "Shakespeare's Merchant of Venice," May 6-7, year [1935?] (2 copies)
Shadows, "Shakespeare's 'Hamlet,'" April 28-29, 1936
Shadows, "Pride and Prejudice," April 22-23, 1937
Senior Class, "Mrs. Bumpstead - Leigh: A Comedy in Three Acts," November 22, 1937
Shadows, "Pomander Walk," November 17-18,1938
Shadows, "Cyrano de Bergerac", February 24 and 25, 1941
Shadows, Play "Murder in the Cathedral", March 18 and 19, 1946
Shadows, "Paul Claudel's 'Tidings Brought to Mary,'" November 13-14, 1958
Shadows, "A Song at the Scaffold." March 15 and 16, year?
European Trips
Moved to file: European Tours
Invitation to attend the 1960 European tour
Folder containing brochures, correspondence, and itineraries relating to the 1965 trip to Europe and the 1967 trip to Europe and the Holy Land
Letter from Sister Mary Ancilla, regarding updates on the 1967 tour, June 1, 1967
Itinerary for the 1971 European Study Tour
Events with William Kennedy Moved to file: Kennedy, William J.
"William Kennedy's Albany. Weekend Celebration," program, September 6-9, 1984
"An Evening of Conversation with William Kennedy," program, February 6, 1985
"An Evening of Conversation with William Kennedy," poster, February 6, 1985 (3 copies)
Fiftieth Anniversary Celebration
Moved to: Fiftieth Anniversary Celebration Records
"Anniversary Announcement: 50, 1920-1970. Vision 2020: Each Man Makes Wide His World." (4 copies)
"College of Saint Rose Anniversary Calendar 1970-1971
Invitation to the "Golden Jubilee Dinner," March 19, 1971
"Golden Jubilee Dinner," Menu and program, March 19, 1971 (2 copies)
"Fiftieth Anniversary Convocation and Inauguration," Program, March 19, 1971
Alumni Association, "In Celebration of 50 Years of Saint Rose Alumni," 1974 pamphlet (2 copies)
Founders' Day Events
Moved to: Founders' Day folder
"Saint Rose and Founders' Day," Program, January 22, 1958 (2 copies)
"Sixth Annual Founders' Dinner," Program, November 29, 1990
Library Dedication Moved to Library Records
"Saint Rose Library," booklet, 1950 (2 copie)
"The Sisters of Saint Joseph announce the Dedication of the Library," program, October 21,1951
May Day
Moved to the May Day folder
• "May Day, Marian Year, 1954" Program
• "May Day Headquarters," General Information, 1956 May Day
Music
Moved to Music Collection
"Recital," February 23, 1922
"Graduation Repertoire," May 24, 1928
Choir with Selected Male Chorus, "Elijah," April 21, 1929
Miss Rita M. Donohue & Miss Mary J. Bicak, "Piano Repertoire," May 22, 1930 (2 copies)
"Stell Andersen, Pianist," March 5, 1931
"Musicale,"Mayl5, 1931
"Piano Repertoire," May 21, 1931
Members of the Music Department and Glee Club, "The Chimes of Normandy: A Comic Opera in Three Acts by Robert Planquette," April 18-19, 1932
"Chimes of Normandy," Undated. Typed description of acts and cast of characters, [likely 1932]
Graduates of the Department of Music, "Program of Piano Concertos," May 26, 1932
"Mary Becker, Violinist," December 2, 1932
Members of the Music Department and the Glee Club, "The Gondoliers: A Comic
Opera by Gilbert and Sullivan," May 8, 10, 12, [1933]
Graduates of the Department of Music, "Recital," May 26, 1933
Choir with Male Chorus and Soloists, "Stabat Mater," March 9, 1934
Department of Music and Glee Club, "The Yeomen of the Guard: Comic Opera by Gilbert and Sullivan," May 16-18, 1934
"Hilger Trio," November 14, 1934
Choir, Male Chorus, and Soloists, "A.M.D.G. Choral Concert," April 4, 1935
Miss Virginia A. Schiele, "Recital," May 24, 1935
Department of Music and Glee Club, "lolanthe: Comic Opera by Gilbert & Sullivan," November 21-22, 1935
"Song Recital...Alice C. Cooper, Soprano," May 15, 1936
Graduates of the Department of Music, "Recital," May 23, 1936
Albany Concert Orchestra and CSR Choir, "Concert," March 22, 1938
Department of Music and Glee Club, "Patience: Comic Opera by Gilbert & Sullivan," April 27-28, 1939 (3 copies)
Graduates of the Department of Music, "Recital," June 1, 1939 (2 copies)
Graduates of the Department of Music, "Recital," May 29, 1940
Graduates of the Department of Music, "Recital Program," May 20, 1942 (2 copies)
Glee Club, Christmas Concert, December 14, 1943
Graduates of the Department of Music, "Graduation Repertoire Program," May 17,1944
Albany Diocesan Unit, National Catholic Music Educators' Association, Program, September 16, 1944 (2 copies)
Glee Club, Concert at Union College, April 16, 1945
Glee Club, Jubilee Concert, May 9, 1945 (2 copies)
Albany Diocesan Unit of the National Catholic Music Educators' Association, Music Demonstration Program, May 20, 1945 (2 copies)
Glee Club, Christmas Concert, December 11, 1945
Students of the Music Department, "The Gondoliers: A Comic Opera by Gilbert & Sullivan," November 20-22, 1946
Troy Chapter of College of Saint Rose Alumnae, "College Glee Club," December 11, 1946
Glee Clubs (Saint Rose & Fordham University), "Combined Concert," May 14, 1947
Graduates of the Department of Music, "Piano Repertoire," May 20, 1947 (6 copies)
Glee Club, "Christmas Concert," December 16, 1947
Students of the Music Department, "lolanthe: Comic Opera by Gilbert & Sullivan," November 17-19,1948 (2 copies)
"Christmas Concert," December 14, 1948
Glee Club, "Christmas Concert," December 12, 1950
Graduates of the Department of Music, "Two Evenings of Musical Repertoire," May 6 and May 13,1951 (2 copies)
Glee Club, "Christmas Concert," December 12, 1952
Glee Clubs (College of Saint Rose & Manhattan College), "Joint Concert," April 17, 1953
Department of Music Students, "Two Evenings of Musical Repertoire," May 12-13, 1953
Glee Club, "Patience: a Comic Opera by Gilbert & Sullivan," November 19 and 20,1953 (2 copies)
Department of Music, "Two Evenings of Musical Repertoire," May 15-16, 1957
Music Department, "Hansel and Gretel," November 14-15, 1957
Department of Music, "Musical Repertoire," May 6-7, 1958
Glee Clubs (College of Saint Rose & Fordham University), "Annual Concert," March 25, 1960
Department of Music, "Two Evenings of Musical Repertoire," May 17, 1961
Glee Clubs (College of Saint Rose & United States Military Academy at West Point), "Spring Concert," May 2, 1970
Music Department, "Sister Martha Anna Wachtel, CSJ in a Fiftieth Anniversary Faculty Concert," November 22, 1970
Glee Club and Schola of Our Lady of Angels Seminary, "A Christmas Carol," December 13, 1970
College of Saint Rose featuring the New York State Philharmonia, "A Beethoven Valentine," February 14, 1971
Music Department, "Patricia Brady Danzig '53 in a German Recital," May 9, 1971
Danzig, Patricia Brady, [Untitled Program], February 13, 1976
"Hooked on Swing," May 4, 1984
"Patricia Brady-Danzig Performance Hall Dedication Concert," November 15, 1992 (2 copies)
Music Department, "24th Annual Spring Concert of the Masterworks Chorale & Orchestra," May 1, 1995
Music Department, "Christmas Carol," December 16, year?
"The History of the Music Department, The College of Saint Rose, 1920-1992," presented on the occasion of a concert by Patricia Brady-Danzig and the dedication of the Patricia Brady-Danzig Performance Hall. (2 copies)
President's Receptions
Moved to: [NOT RECORDED BY PROCESSOR]
Invitation, President's Reception, December 16, undated
Invitation, President's Reception, January 12, 1986
Rosa Mystica Unveiling
Moved to: Rosa Mystica file
"Ceremony of Unveiling of a Statue of 'Rosa Mystica,'" Program, May 28, 1939 (5 copies)
Seventy-fifth Anniversary Celebration
Moved to: Seventy-fifth Anniversary Celebration Records
Golden Roses Liturgy Program, June 10,1994
Golden Roses Liturgy Program, June 9, 1995
Toward Tomorrow Campaign
Moved to: Toward Tomorrow Campaign file
CSR Toward Tomorrow Campaign Newsletter, Volume 1, Number 1
CSR Toward Tomorrow Campaign Newsletter, Volume 1, Number 2
Traditions Directions Capital Campaign
Moved to Office of Development, 1964 -: Traditions Directions Campaign
Invitation, Traditions Directions Capital Campaign, December 15, 1987
From Series 9: College of Saint Rose Commencement Programs and Commencement-related Materials
Moved to Commencement Collection
Invitation to Commencement Exercises, to be held June 15,1927
Commencement Exercises Overview, June 10-15, 1927
Commencement Exercises Program, June 12, 1929
Class Night Exercises Program, Class of 1930, June 10, 1930
Commencement Exercises Program, June 12, 1930
Class Night Exercises Program, Class of 1931, June 5, 1931
Commencement Exercises Program, June 10, 1931
Invitation to Commencement on June 13, 1932
Commencement Exercises Overview, June 7-13, 1932
Class Night Exercises Program, Class of 1932, June 10, 1932
Commencement Exercises Program, June 13, 1932
Commencement Exercises Program, June 13, 1934
Commencement Exercises Overview, June 8-13, 1935
Commencement Exercises Program, June 13, 1935
Commencement Exercises Overview, June 6-10, 1936
Class Night Exercises Program, Class of 1937, June 7, 1937
Commencement Exercises Program, June 9, 1937
Invitation to Commencement Exercises, to be held June 9, 1938
Commencement Exercises Overview, June 2-9, 1938
Class Night Exercises, Class of 1938, June 7, 1938
Commencement Exercises Program, June 9, 1938
Moving Up Night Program, Class of 1939, June 2, 1939 (2 copies)
Class Night Exercises Program, Class of 1939, June 5, 1939
Commencement Exercises Program, June 7, 1939 (3 copies)
Commencement Exercises Program, October 29, 1939
Class Night Exercises Program, Class of 1940, June 3, 1940
Moving Up Night Program, Class of 1945
Class Night Exercises, Program, June 4, 1945 (2 copies)
Commencement Exercises, Invitation, June 5, 1945
Graduation Repertoire, May 22, 1946
23r Commencement Exercises Program, June 11, 1947
Commencement Exercises Program, June 9, 1948
Class Night Exercises, Program, June 6, 1949
Graduation Repertoire, Program, May 9 and 10, 1950
Moving Up Night Program, Class of 1950, June 2, 1950
Baccalaureate Exercises Program, June 4, 1950 (3 copies)
Address to the Graduating Class by John F. Brosnan, June 7, 1950 (4 copies)
27th Commencement Exercises Program, June 7, 1950
Moving Up Night Program, Class of 1951, June 1, 1951
Baccalaureate Exercises Program, June 3, 1951 (3 copies)
Class Night Exercises Program, Class of 1951, June 4, 1951 (2 copies)
28th Commencement Exercises Program, June 6, 1951 (2 copies)
30th Commencement Exercises Program, June 3, 1953
Baccalaureate Exercises Program, June 2, 1957
Commencement Exercises Program, June 5, 1957 (2 copies)
Class Night Exercises, Class of 1958, June 2, 1958
Baccalaureate Exercises Program, June 4, 1961
Commencement Exercises, June 5, 1961
48th Annual Commencement Exercises Program, May 22, 1971 (2 copies)
53rd Annual Commencement Exercises Program, May 22, 1976
College of Saint Rose Commencement, Invitation, May 1, 1977
67th Annual Commencement Exercises Program, May 12, 1990 (3 copies)
Golden Rose Liturgy, Program, June 9, 1995
From Series 10; College of Saint Rose College Catalogs
Moved to the Catalog Collection
[Catalog], 1922-1923
[Catalog], 1923-1924
[Catalog/Brochure], 1935
Undergraduate Catalog, 1970-1971
From Series 12: College of Saint Rose Alumni Association
Alumni Directories
Moved to Alumni Publications: Alumni Directories
College of Saint Rose Alumnae Association Directory Constitution and By-Laws, 1954